A racing second hand, a shooting comet, a wind-up doll, and a crowd!
،عقرب دقائق مسرِع، مُذنّب ساقط دمية آلية الخروج، وحشد ناس
Mystery-solving logic drenches dry hearts and sand walls!
تبلل الاستنتاجات المفككة للغموض أسوار القلوب الجافة
Today's case is about greed and 1 billion yen in gold!
!قضيّة اليوم عن الطمع! مليار ينّ ذهباً
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!إنّه المتحرّي كونان
The Ryujin-Maru disappeared seven years ago
ريوجين مارو التي اختفت قبل 7 أعوام
with 1 billion yen in gold onboard, but suddenly reappeared!
وعلى متنها مليار ينّ ذهباً عاودت الظهور على جزيرة شيكي فجأةً
But the gold was gone.
لكنّ الذهب اختفى
The old man was invited to the island, which had garnered attention
دُعي العمّ للجزيرة التي جذبت انتباهاً
because of the ghost ship.
بسبب سفينة الأشباح
We came here as tourists, but the mayor's true motive
...أتينا كسيّاح، لكنّ دافع العمدة الحقيقيّ
was to have the old man locate the missing gold.
كان جعل العمّ يجد مكان الذهب المفقود
Someone tried to kill him at his lecture.
حاول أحدهم قتله أثناء محاضرته
The culprit was Hamada, the lighthouse keeper with facial burns.
كان الفاعل هامادا، حارس المنارة بحروق الوجه
And the suspicious travel agent Uehara seemed to know him.
وبدا أنّ موظف وكالة السفر المشبوه المدعوّ أويهارا يعرفه
Who exactly are these two?
من هذان الاثنان بالضبط؟
That night, the old man was attacked by a warrior.
تعرّض العمّ تلك الليلة للهجوم من قبل مُحارب
After narrowly escaping death, he chased his assailant.
ولاحقه بعدما نجا من الموت بصعوبة
Someone knocked him unconscious and framed him...
...أفقده أحدهم وعيه ونصب له فخّاً
...as Hamada's killer!
فجعله قاتل هامادا
The Ghost Ship Murder Case (Part 2)
(جريمة قتل سفينة الأشباح (الجزء الثاني
Mori-san!
!موري-سان
Even if you're a famous detective,
حتّى لو كنت متحرّياً شهيراً
you can't get away with murder!
!لا يمكنك أن تفلت بجريمة قتل
You got it all wrong! This guy suddenly attacked me in my sleep!
الأمر ليس هكذا! هاجمني هذا الشخص !فجأةً أثناء نومي
I chased him here, got hit from behind,
لاحقتُه إلى هنا، وضُربت من مؤخرة رأسي
and when I woke up he was dead!
!وعندما أفقت كان على حاله هذه
You probably just killed him in a rage!
قتلته في نوبة غضبك غالباً
I didn't do it!
!أخبرتك كلا
But this outfit he's wearing is kept in
...لكنّ الدرع الذي يرتديه كان مُحتفظاً به
the Suigun Artifact Museum...
في متحف أثريات سويغون
Why another Suigun outfit?
لمَ درع سويغون آخر؟
Could it be the curse?!
أيمكن أنّها اللعنة؟
Don't be a fool!
!لا تكن أحمق
No, it has to be!
!كلا، لا بدّ أنّها هي
I bet Hamada got possessed and dressed up like this!
!مُسَّ هامادا ودُفِع لارتداء هذا الزيّ حتماً
Be quiet! The curse is just a superstition!
!اصمتوا! اللعنة مجرد خرافة
Then why's he dressed like that?!
!لمَ يرتدي هامادا هذا الدرع إذاً؟
Well, that's--
...في الواقع، هذا
Now, now. There's no point in arguing here.
مهلكم، لا جدوى من الجدال هنا
This sword wound is what killed him.
طعنة السيف هذه هي ما قتله
Did his sleeve come off during the struggle?
هل نُزعت أكمامه أثناء الصراع؟
Those are rope marks!
!آثار تقييد
Covered in cuts. But these ones are--
...تغطيه الجروح، لكنّ هذه
Children shouldn't look at such things.
على الأطفال ألّا يروا أشياء كهذه
Yeah!
...أ-أجل
Wait! Where are you going, Conan-kun?
لحظة، أين تذهب يا كونان-كن؟
Conan-kun! You'll get in trouble for barging in here!
كونان-كن! ستقع في مشكلة !إن دخلت هكذا
No doubt about it. Hamada-san was killed here!
!لا شكّ في الأمر، قُتل هامادا-سان هنا
It's dry.
جافّ
Is that blood?!
أهذا دم؟
Ran! Get that officer!
!ران-نيتشان! استدعي الشرطيّ
It does look like he was murdered here.
يبدو أنّه قُتل هنا بالفعل
But that doesn't clear the detective's name...
...لكنّ ذلك لا يُبرئ ساحة المتحرّي
But...
...لكن
The ghosts got mad because an outsider was poking around!
غضب سويغون-ساما بسبب عبث !دخيل في الأرجاء
Hold on...
...انتظروا
You're gonna protect him?!
!ستحميه؟
You'll be cursed too, you know!
!ستصيبك لعنة سويغون-ساما أيضاً هكذا
Hey, you! Stop that!
!أنتم! توقفوا
This doesn't look good...
...الوضع سيّئ هكذا
There it is!
!ها هي
What? What's here? The Suigun?!
!ماذا؟ ما الذي يجري؟! سويغون-ساما؟
Hilarious.
يا للسخرية
Come again?!
ما-ماذا؟
I don't know who did it, but if they think they can frame me
لا أعرف من وراء هذا، لكن إن ظنّ بإمكانه تلفيق تهمة بي
with such a childish trick, they're greatly mistaken!
بحيلة طفولية كهذه، فقد اقترف خطأً فادحاً
You mean you didn't do this?!
!تقصد أنّك لم تكن الفاعل؟
Of course I didn't!
بالطبع لا
He was dead long before I got here.
كان ميتاً قبل وصولي هنا
Don't give us that crap!
!هراء
The pool of blood on the boat is proof.
دليل ذلك هي بركة الدم على القارب
If I killed him, then he only died thirty minutes ago!
إذا كنتُ قد قتلته، فيُفترض أنّ ذلك كان قبل 30 دقيقة
But the blood on the boat is completely dry!
لكنّ الدم على القارب جاف تماماً
However you look at it, three to four hours have passed!
كيفما نظرتم للأمر، فقد مضت 3 إلى 4 ساعات
Now that you mention it--
...صـ-صحيح
My attacker was someone other than Hamada.
من هاجمني كان شخصاً غير هامادا
That person killed him!
هو من قتل هامادا
After killing him, they attacked me in Suigun armor!
بعد قتله له، هاجمني بدرع سويغون
To lure me here and frame me as Hamada's murderer.
لاستدراجي هنا وجعلي أبدو قاتل هامادا
But...
...لكن
That person tied Hamada up in the boat and tortured him!
قيّد ذاك الشخص هامادا في القارب وعذّبه
The rope marks on his wrists are proof!
ودليل ذلك هي آثار الحبل على معصميه
And the cuts all over his body are too numerous and shallow to be fatal.
كما الجروح التي تغطي جسده كثيرة وسطحية على أن تكون مُميتة
He's right!
مـ-معه حق
In other words, the killer tied him up and tortured him.
أي أنّ القاتل قيّد هامادا وعذّبه
Who'd do something so horrible?!
لمَ قد يفعل شيئاً بهذه الفظاعة؟
Hamada was probably connected to the Ryujin-Maru.
كان لهامادا علاقة بريوجين مارو غالباً
He was probably on it!
لعلّه كان على متنها
How do you know about that?!
!وما أدراك بذلك؟
The Ryujin-Maru's telescope was on the lighthouse.
كان منظار ريوجين مارو على المنارة
Eh? How do you know about that?
ماذا؟ كيف عرفت ذلك؟
Uh oh!
!تبّاً
There's nothing a great detective doesn't know!
!لا شيء يخفى على المتحرّي العظيم
Say, Hamada appeared seven years ago, too...
بالمناسبة، ظهر هامادا قبل 7 أعوام أيضاً
So it was the gold's location that the killer got from Hamada?
كان القاتل يستخرج موقع الذهب من هامادا إذاً؟
Yes. Hamada most likely knew where it was.
أجل، كان هامادا يعرف مكانه على الأغلب
And he moved to the island to guard it.
وانتقل لهذه الجزيرة لحراسته
But he feared I would find it, so he attempted to kill me.
لكنّه خشي أن أجده بعدما ظهرتُ فجأةً، فحاول قتلي
Conan and Suzu-kun even saw him leave from the backstage door.
رآه كونان وسوزو-كن يغادر من الباب الخلفيّ للمسرح أيضاً
Suzu did?
سوزو؟
But there was yet another person looking for the gold.
لكن كان هناك شخصاً آخر يبحث عن الذهب
In that person's eyes, Hamada and I were both obstacles.
في نظره، كنتُ وهامادا عقبتين أمامه
That would explain the set up here!
يفسّر ذلك مكيدته هنا
But there's no one here like that--
...لـ-لكن لا يوجد شخص كهذا من أهل الجزيرة
It's him! That other person from Tokyo!
!ذاك الشخص! من أتى من طوكيو
The travel agent?!
عامل وكالة السفر؟
He was fighting with Hamada!
!كان يتشاجر مع هامادا
What?
مـ-ماذا؟
Where is he staying?
أين يقيم؟
The inn, I think.
في النُزل وفقما أظن
That's great, Dad!
هذا رائع يا أبي
I didn't do it! Believe me!
!لم أكن الفاعل! صدّقوني
No, we know you didn't!
نعرف ذلك الآن
Officer! Get going!
!أيّها الشرطيّ، أسرع
We've never arrested anyone before!
!لـ-لم يسبق وأن اعتقلنا مجرماً
Geez. What're you here for then?
يا إلهي، لمَ أنت هنا إذاً؟
What's the matter?
ما الخطب؟
He's got cold feet!
إنّه خائف
I shall go.
سأذهب أنا
Deputy Mayor!
!نائب العمدة
I'll try to convince him to turn himself in.
سأحاول إقناعه بتسليم نفسه
But...
...لـ-لكن
It was the town hall that asked him here.
كانت البلدية من استدعته هنا
It's my responsibility as Deputy Mayor.
لذا هي مسؤوليتي كنائب العمدة
It's been five minutes now...
...مضت 5 دقائق
Kinoshita-san!
!كينوشيتا-سان
Are you alright?!
أأنت بخير؟
He ran off...
...هرب
He escaped out the back! After him!
!فرّ من الخلف! الحقوا به
I tried to persuade him, but he suddenly shot at me...
...حاولتُ إقناعه، لكنه أطلق عليّ النار فجأةً
We need to get you to a doctor!
!علينا أخذك للطبيب فوراً
I'll be all right. It's just a scratch.
لا بأس، إنّه مجرد خدش
No sign of him around the back road. Go ahead.
لا أثر له على الطريق الخلفي، حوّل
No sign of him here either. Go ahead.
لا أثر له هنا أيضاً، حوّل
Good work. Sorry, but could you leave some guards
عمل موفق، أعتذر لكن هلّا تركتما حرّاساً
and come back for now?
ورجعتما إلى هنا حالياً؟
Hey, now! There's still this area!
انتظر! بقيت هذه المنطقة
You can't ask us to check the Suigun Cave...
...لا يمكننا تفقّد كهف سويغون
Nobody would dare go near that place. A single officer isn't really--
،لن يقترب أحد من أهل الجزيرة منه ...لا يمكن لمجرّد شرطيّ واحد
What kind of cowardice is this?!
!أيّ جُبن هذا؟
Then why don't you go?!
!لمَ لا تذهب أنت إذاً؟
Get serious! Why me?
سخافة! لمَ أنا؟
If Uehara killed Hamada-san, he must've learned the gold's location.
إذا قتل أويهارا هامادا-سان، فلا بدّ أنه عرف مكان الذهب
But if so, then why did he need to search the lighthouse?
لكن في تلك الحالة، لمَ كان عليه تفتيش المنارة؟
No Entrance
الدخول ممنوع
Moss?
طُحلب
And this is the kind that grows on land!
!وهذا من الصنف الذي ينمو على الأرض
I was right; this boat didn't sink!
لم يغرق هذا القارب بالفعل إذاً
But would it be possible to hide it from the islanders for seven years?!
لكن هل سيمكن إخفاؤه عن أنظار أهل الجزيرة لسبعة أعوام؟
Wait a minute!
...لحظة
There's the Suigun Cave.
ذاك كهف سويغون
No one would go near there! What if--
...لا يقترب أحد من هناك، أيمكن
He would've noticed it had he looked through the telescope!
...كان ليلاحظ لو نظر من المنظار
There was no need to torture Hamada-san!
لم يكن هناك داعٍ لتعذيب هامادا-سان
Suigun Cave
كهف سويغون
Not good. I'll get stopped if I'm seen.
هذا سيّئ، سيوقفونني إذا رأوني
Oh, it's just you.
...أنت فحسب
Don't you 'oh' me! You wanna go to the cave, don't you?
ما قصدك؟! تريد الذهاب للكهف، صحيح؟
Yeah.
أجل
I happen to know a secret path.
أعرف طريقاً سرّياً
What?!
ماذا؟
Where?! Tell me!
!أين؟! أخبريني
How rude! Can't you ask politely?
أهكذا تسأل؟! أين الأدب؟
Please.
من فضلك
That's all?
فقط؟
What else should I do?!
ماذا تريدين أيضاً؟
You dummy! What're you thinking?!
حـ-حمقاء! ما الذي تفكّرين به؟
If you don't want to, then fine.
لا بأس إذا لم تكن تريد
Darn it...
...تبّاً
Here is fine.
هنا إذاً
OK! I'll show you the way! Follow me!
!حسناً، سأرشدك! اتبعني
What a bossy kid...
...طفلة متسلّطة
See! Here it is!
!هنا! ها هو
You're not going in, are you?
لن تدخل، صحيح؟
I am.
بلى
But...
...لكن
I thought you didn't believe in superstitions?
ظننتك لا تؤمنين بالخرافات
Of course I don't! I only asked because I'm concerned about you!
بالطبع لا! سألتُ لأنّي قلقة عليك فحسب
You can stay here if you're scared.
يمكنك البقاء هنا إن كنتِ خائفة
Wait!
!انتظر
It's just a superstition, right?
إنّها مجرد خرافة، صحيح؟
It looks like Hamada-san used to look after this.
يبدو أنّ المقتول هامادا-سان كان يعتني بهذا
The ghosts are mad!
!سويغون-ساما غاضب
Conan-kun! You'll be punished!
!كونان-كن! ستُعاقب
Another cave.
كهف آخر
Those weren't ghosts just now.
لم يكن ذاك صوت غضب سويغون
It was just a draft resonating inside the cave.
بل تيّار هوائي يرتدّ بأرجاء الكهف
Are we going in?
سندخل؟
Yeah.
أجل
These stairs aren't natural. Someone purposely made them.
هذه الأدراج ليست طبيعية، بل صنعها أحدهم
It's bright up ahead!
ضوء في الأسفل
You should make stairs that don't break, you know?
ما خطب هذه الأدراج؟ عليك بناؤها بحيث لا تنهار
This moss! This is the place!
!هذا الطُحلب، هذا هو المكان إذاً
Is this--
...أهذا
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
It's so pretty!
!المكان جميل جدّاً
There's no moss here. It broke apart recently.
لا طحالب هنا، انهار مؤخراً
Ah. The storm opened up the exit and--
...فهمت، فتحت العاصفة المخرج و
Looks like something slid down.
أثر انزلاج شيء
No doubt about it. The Ryujin-Maru was hidden here.
لا شكّ في الأمر، كانت ريوجين مارو مخبّأة هنا
The passageway that the Ryujin-Maru stayed in
المعبر الذي كانت ريوجين مارو داخله
was demolished by the storm and reopened.
هدمته العاصفة ففُتح مُجدداً
What is it?!
!ما الخطب؟
A suicide?!
انتحار؟
No, this was no suicide! In which case, the killer is--
...كلا، لم يكن انتحاراً! ما يعني أنّ القاتل
Hello? Yes. Yes.
مرحباً؟ أجل، أجل
That would really help us out!
!سيساعدنا ذلك كثيراً
Yes. Thanks a lot.
أجل، شكراً
Detective Mori! The fishermen are going to lend us a boat
متحرّي موري! سيعيرنا الصيّادون قارباً
to go by the Suigun Cave!
لنذهب لكهف سويغون
Alright! Let's go, Ran!
!حسنٌ، هيّا بنا يا ران
Wait, Dad! Have you seen Conan-kun?
انتظر يا أبي! هل رأيت كونان-كن؟
Who cares?! He's probably off playing somewhere!
من يهتم؟ إنّه يعبث في الأرجاء غالباً
Now hurry!
!أسرعي وحسب
He probably killed himself after accepting that he couldn't escape.
انتحر بعد تقبّل أنّ لم يعد بإمكانه الهروب غالباً
Kinoshita-san...
...كينوشيتا-سان
I followed you when I saw you go inside.
تبعتكما بعدما رأيتكما تدخلان
Well, let's go back to town.
هيّا، لنرجع للبلدة
Yeah.
أجل
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
This was no suicide. He was murdered.
لم ينتحر هذا الرجل، بل قُتل
You can't be serious!
!لا يُعقل
Look at his wound.
انظر لجرحه
The hole on the right is bigger than the one on the left.
الفجوة على اليمين أكبر من التي على اليسار
This proves the bullet went from left to right.
هذا دليل أنّ الطلقة عبرت من اليسار لليمين
Yet the gun is in his right hand.
مع ذلك المسدّس في يده اليمنى
Isn't it unnatural to shoot from the left with your right hand?
أليس غريباً أن تُطلق من اليسار بيدك اليمنى؟
In that case, there's no longer any need to hide the truth.
في تلك الحالة، لم تعد هناك حاجة لإخفاء الحقيقة
Why?!
لمَ؟
Conan-kun doesn't seem surprised.
لا تبدو الدهشة على كونان-كن
You shot yourself in the arm, didn't you?
أطلقت على ذراعك بنفسك، صحيح؟
You even realized that?!
أدركت ذلك حتّى؟
There were burn marks on the hole in your shirt.
كانت هناك آثار احتراق على الفجوة بقميصك
Which means that you fired with the muzzle pressed against it.
ما يعني أنّك أطلقت والفوهة عليها تماماً
You said that you were suddenly shot at.
قلتَ أنّه أطلق النار عليك فجأةً
Nobody would 'suddenly' shoot in such a way.
لا أحد يطلق النار "فجأةً" هكذا
You impress me.
أذهلتني، أنت مُبهر
You also killed Hamada-san.
أنت من قتل هامادا-سان أيضاً
That's right. I always thought he seemed suspicious.
صحيح، لطالما بدا لي مريباً
So I checked the lighthouse while he was gone.
فتفقدت المنارة في غيابه
I take it you found the telescope?
ووجدت المنظار، صحيح؟
Yes. I planned to look for the gold someday at my leisure.
أجل، خطّطت للبحث عن الذهب يوماً ما على مهلي
But the greedy mayor started needlessly prying...
...لكنّ العمدة الطمّاع بدأ يتدخل
Daddy's not greedy! He said you used the town's money!
!أبي ليس طمّاعاً! قال أنّك استغللت مال البلدة
I became nervous; Kogoro Mori is a peerless detective.
أصبحتُ متوتراً، فموري كوغورو مُتحرٍّ عظيم
I was worried he might find the gold first if he started investigating.
خشيت أن يجد الذهب قبلي إن بدأ التحقيق
And he got involved, too.
وفوقها تدخل هذا الشخص أيضاً
So you tricked the old man and framed him as Hamada-san's killer.
لذا خدعت العمّ وجعلته يبدو قاتل هامادا-سان
I mistakenly underestimated him, though.
لكنّي أخطأت في التقليل من شأنه
But you did learn the gold's location from Hamada-san...
لكنّك عرفت موقع الذهب من هامادا-سان
He finally told me about this place after a bit of pain.
أخبرني أخيراً عن هذا المكان بعدما عذّبته بما يكفي
Just as Mori said, he had been on the Ryujin-Maru.
كما قال موري، لقد كان على متن ريوجين مارو
I take it this guy was, too?
وكذلك هذا الشخص كما أظن، صحيح؟
Yes. Hamada threw him and the owner into the stormy ocean
أجل، دفعه هامادا مع المالك في المحيط العاصف
to keep all the gold for himself.
ليحتكر الذهب لنفسه
Hamada. His real name was apparently Aoki.
هامادا، اسمه الحقيقيّ آوكي وفقما يبدو
He brought the Ryujin-Maru in here to escape the storm.
جلب ريوجين مارو هنا للاحتماء من العاصفة
But the storm tore rocks off and sealed the exit.
لكنّ العاصفة أسقطت الصخور وأغلقت المخرج
He probably didn't plan to, but there were no other hiding places.
لم تكن نيّته غالباً، لكن لم تكن هناك أماكن إخفاء أخرى
The islanders stayed away because of the 'curse.'
ابتعد أهل القرية بسبب اللعنة
Even more so after he killed the professor to make it look like
خصوصاً بعدما قتل هامادا البروفسور ليجعلها
the Suigun curse.
تبدو من صنيع لعنة سويغون
What happened to his face?
ما حلّ بوجهه؟
I hear he burned it himself
سمعتُ أنّه حرقه بنفسه
because he feared someone might recognize him...
لأنّه خشي أن يتعرّف أحد عليه
You pretended to get shot by Uehara-san to let him escape, huh?
تظاهرت بتعرضك للإصابة بطلقة كي تجعل أويهارا-سان يهرب، صحيح؟
If he were arrested, Hamada-san's killer and the gold's location
فإذا اُعتقل كنّا سنعرف هويّة قاتل هامادا-سان
would be found out.
كما موقع الذهب
That's right. He did seem vaguely aware of this place.
صحيح، بدا أنّه يدرك وجود هذا المكان لحدٍّ ما
Why are you letting me run?
لـ-لمَ تتركني أهرب؟
Never mind that; you're a dead man if they catch you now!
!لا تهتم، ستلقى حتفك إن أمسكوا بك
I'll hold onto this.
سأبقيه معي
Your situation will get even worse if you're caught with it.
ستكون في ورطة أكبر لو وجدوه معك
Thanks...
...شـ-شكراً
Kinoshita-san!
!كينوشيتا-سان
Then you beat him to the cave and killed him.
ثمّ سبقته للكهف وقتلته
That's right. Now our discussion is over!
صحيح، انتهى نقاشنا الآن
Nobody'll find your bodies here! Ever!
!لن يجد أحد جثّتيكما هنا! أبداً
Conan-kun!
...كونان-كن
Did you find the gold?
أوجدت الذهب؟
It's probably buried around here somewhere.
إنّه مدفون في مكان ما هنا بالتأكيد
I'll leisurely look for it after things cool down.
سأبحث عنه على مهلي بعدما تهدأ الأوضاع
What's so funny?!
!ما الذي يضحكك؟
You'd never find it in 100 years with your intelligence!
لن تجده بعقلك هذا ولو بعد 100 سنة
What did you say?!
!ماذا؟
You still don't know?
لم تعرفه بعد؟
You mean you know where?!
!أي عرفت؟
Yeah. At your feet.
أجل، عند قدميك
Go!
!انطلقي
The gold was in these blocks used as part of the stairs.
كان الذهب في هذه القراميد التي اُستعملت كجزء من الأدراج
Wow! I love you, Conan-kun!
!مذهل! أحبّك يا كونان-كن
Hey, now...
...أنت
An earthquake?!
!هزّة؟
There it is!
ها هو
Take this board to the exit! I'll bring Kinoshita-san!
!خذي اللوح للمخرج! سأجلب كينوشيتا-سان
Right!
حسناً
Conan-kun! Hurry!
!كونان-كن! أسرع
Hurry!
!أسرع! أسرع
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
There's probably no way to dig out the gold
لم تعد هناك طريقة لاستخراج الذهب
in the completely-collapsed cave.
من الكهف المنهار كليّاً الآن غالباً
I doubt anyone would spend over a billion yen
أشكّ بأن ينفق أحد ما يفوق مليار ينّ
just to dig out a billion yen.
لاستخراج مجرّد مليار ينّ
In the end, the greed-inducing gold returned to the earth,
في النهاية، رجع الذهب الذي أوقد الطمع بالناس للأرض
along with the Suigun curse.
مع لعنة سويغون
You idiot! If I hadn't gone to rescue you in the fishing boat,
،أيّها الغبيّ! لو لم آت لإنقاذك بقارب صيد
there's no telling what would've happened!
!من يعرف ما كان سيحلّ بك؟
What are you doing to my Conan-kun?!
!ماذا تفعل لعزيزي كونان-كن؟
Yikes!
...مخيفة
It's empty!
!إ-إنّه فارغ
I don't get it! Where did the killer disappear to?!
لا  أفهم، أين اختفى القاتل؟
Wait! Could it be?! Only he could've done it!
لحظة، في هذه الحالة لا يمكن !أن يكون القاتل سوى ذاك الشخص
The Giant Monster Gomera Murder Case
جريمة قتل الوحش العملاق غوميرا
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Paint.
طلاء
Next episode Genta the kaiju makes his appearance.
يظهر في الحلقة القادمة !الوحش الكبير، غينتا
Eel bowls!
!أنقليس